{
    "id": "6dfc419c5a3f48c58328652b543900a5",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "People ran for shelter, ………………… the storm broke out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "when",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "47843f9fd30e41c6866c53c3360ceb77"
        },
        {
            "question": "The audience left the hall ……………… the performance was over. (time)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "when",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9345632554d84f4fa6a7b28bed6da18e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Go ………………… you like. (place)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "where",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "523fd52b479d4323ac0568996a02090b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The accident occurred ……………….. the four roads meet. (place)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "when",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0f82e42e1e3e4c4e9f4f310a52a15ab8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train cannot start …………………. the signal is given.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "before",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "66d32a664606434387f71ed95538fa25"
        },
        {
            "question": "His wife fainted ………………….. she heard the news. (time)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "where",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b54612887324485ca61e6731d225beff"
        },
        {
            "question": "We eat ………………… we may live.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "that",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e910cc6e971241168cf1c4c62f132478"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wore a coat ………………… he may not catch cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "in order that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c1718d6c6fbe4647bcc560e30a920ebe"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. I finish this book, I will begin another.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No sooner than",
                "As soon as",
                "Scarcely had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3f64f04f5c18488c9bf78b1facea9239"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wouldn’t do it ………………… it were possible.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "even if",
                "even though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4a1b0581a3904ffe8627067c7644fa5c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He looks ………………… he were on the brink of a nervous breakdown.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "As if",
                "As though"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e6c4a7dc4a454fa5bf3c416856e65d60"
        }
    ]
}